

# **Benediktus Zebua**

Junior Full-Stack .NET Developer



## **Education**

2011 -2014 **SMK Swasta Pembda Nias** 

Computer and Network Engineering



## **Experience**

2014 -2015 **Administration Staff** 

SDN 075061 Balodano

Responsible:

Manage employee and student data in Dapodik.

2015 - present

Member of PMKRI

Association of Catholic Students Republic Indonesia (PMKRI) - Bandung Learning to train themselves to speak in public and to hone mentality, morality and intellectual acumen in thinking.



# **Computer Skills**

Back-End : C#, ASP .NET MVC

Database : MS SQL Server

• Front-End : HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript

Code versioning : Git, Github

OS : Windows, Linux

Graphic Design : Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro

**Mobile Development : Xamarin** 

••••

Entry level

# ග

### **Software**

ASP .NET IDE : Microsoft Visual Studio

Database Design : SQL Server Management Studio

••••

Daily Office : Microsoft Office

Text Editor : Sublime Text, Visual Studio Code

••••

Design Tools : Adobe Photoshop

Video Editor : Adobe Premiere Pro



# **Summary**

Highly motivated people want to learn and seek experience in the social and technological world. An IT enthusiast and has a hobby of graphic design, and is now trained as a Junior Full stack .NET Developer certified from Makers Institute Indonesia.



# **Personal Info**

#### **Address**

Jalan Bukit Jarian No.16, Cidadap -Bandung

#### Phone

+62 823 6677 3314

#### E-mail

benediktuszebua@gmail.com

#### Date of birth

06 May 1996

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/benediktus15

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/benediktus



### **Courses**

May 2017 - Aug 2017

Bootcamp .NET Academy at Makers Institute Indonesia



## **Certificates**

Jan 2017

Dale Carnegie Training -Fundamental Leadership Program (Lab Class)



## Languages

Indonesia



**English** 

